designvitality.com 2013-04-15

# DesignVitality Privacy Policy

## Information and Data that may be Collected

  * Design Vitality collects information about your computer (your IP address, browser type, referral visit and visit time) to provide a better user experience. This information will not be sold to any other parties.

## Cookies

  * Design Vitality stores cookies on your computer during your visit and retrieves them upon your return.
  * These cookies are only used to determine if the website has changed since your last visit
  * Our advertisers may also use cookies, which determine whether you have been shown certain ads before.

## Uses of your Personal Data

  * Your personal data will only be used to improve your browsing experience when browsing the website.

## Other Disclosures

  * Design Vitality does not disclose our cookies to third parties

## Security of your Personal Data

  * Design Vitality will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We are not liable for any malicious activity which is out of our control.

## Policy Amendments

  * Design Vitality may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. Users are encouraged to check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

## Your Choices

  * You may decide to disable cookies for this web site if you so choose.

## Recommended Reading

Visit the [Electronic Frontier Foundation](http://www.eff.org/) to find out more about your digital rights. The EFF is a nonprofit group working to protect your digital rights.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us here.
